{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421247884","data":{"timestamp":" 947421247884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421259751","data":{"timestamp":" 947421259751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421271578","data":{"timestamp":" 947421271577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421290838","data":{"timestamp":" 947421290838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n_ipo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421303167","data":{"timestamp":" 947421303166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_aka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421334099","data":{"timestamp":" 947421334099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421341749","data":{"timestamp":" 947421341748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421352957","data":{"timestamp":" 947421352955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421364191","data":{"timestamp":" 947421364189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421380543","data":{"timestamp":" 947421380541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h_ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421395776","data":{"timestamp":" 947421395774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k_ku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421416501","data":{"timestamp":" 947421416499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421428812","data":{"timestamp":" 947421428810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421440781","data":{"timestamp":" 947421440778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421452886","data":{"timestamp":" 947421452883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u_epo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421465830","data":{"timestamp":" 947421465828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421475200","data":{"timestamp":" 947421475198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_c_ake"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421491171","data":{"timestamp":" 947421491169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421500694","data":{"timestamp":" 947421500692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421517323","data":{"timestamp":" 947421517321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421532171","data":{"timestamp":" 947421532168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421556329","data":{"timestamp":" 947421556327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:0.1.3.med.s","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421559042","data":{"timestamp":" 947421559032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" 759a6d89-c0eb-49b6-828e-e65a3e305d12"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_0.1.3.med.s"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_y_ive"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421667194","data":{"timestamp":" 947421667192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421669827","data":{"timestamp":" 947421669825"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" START_ALIPOKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421673208","data":{"timestamp":" 947421673206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421679450","data":{"timestamp":" 947421679447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421686034","data":{"timestamp":" 947421686033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421692828","data":{"timestamp":" 947421692826"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421697582","data":{"timestamp":" 947421697580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZOEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421699753","data":{"timestamp":" 947421699749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWEKA"," userResponse":" KUMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421701001","data":{"timestamp":" 947421700999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKILALIA"," userResponse":" AKILALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421702319","data":{"timestamp":" 947421702317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKEKA"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421705382","data":{"timestamp":" 947421705379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MKEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421708822","data":{"timestamp":" 947421708820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947421710788","data":{"timestamp":" 947421710785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_153314"," gameId":" aead3137-78c4-4aa5-978d-7fba923c105c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akai alipokuwa mdogo mamake alizoea kumweka akilalia mkeka maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAI"," userResponse":" AKAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}